//Quiz questions
var data = [
     {
          number:1
          question:"'In Nausicaa of the Valley of the Wind,' what threatens the existence of humans?"
          answers:[ 'Nausicaa','Erosion','The toxic jungle','The dragons' ]
          correctAnswer:2
     },
     {
          number:2
          question:"How do Mei, Satsuki and their father make the sootballs leave in 'My Neighbor Totoro'?"
          answers:[ 'Crying','Screaming','Laughing','Jumping']
          correctAnswer:2
     },
     {
          number:3
          question:"What animal do Chirhiro's parents both get turned into in 'Spirited Away'?"
          answers:['Pig','Hedgehog','Bunny','Monkey' ]
          correctAnswer:0
     },
     {
          number:4
          question:"What is Kiki's cat named in 'Kiki's Delivery Service'?"
          answers:[ 'Joe','Gigo','Jay','Jiji']
          correctAnswer:3
     },
     {
          number:5
          question:"What natural disaster happened during 'Ponyo on the Cliff by the Sea'?"
          answers:['Earthquake','Tornado','Tsunami','Mudslide']
          correctAnswer:2
     },
     {
          number:6
          question:"What were the pirates trying to steal from Sheeta in 'Laputa: Castle in the Sky'?"
          answers:['Necklace','Bracelet','Earings','Ring']
          correctAnswer:0
     },
     {
          number:7
          question:"Where was Ashitaka's infection spreading from in 'Princess Mononoke'?"
          answers:['His leg','His head','His chest','His arm']
          correctAnswer:3
     },
     {
          number:8
          question:"What color did Nausicaa's dress change in 'Nausicaa of the Valley of the Wind'?"
          answers:['Pink','Orange','Blue','Purple']
          correctAnswer:2
     },
     {
          number:9
          question:"What does Arietty use to hold her hair back in 'The Secret World of Arietty'?"
          answers:['Rubber Band','Clothespin','Ring','Tape']
          correctAnswer:1
     },
     {
          number:10
          question:"What is the flaming creature's name in 'Howl's Moving Castle?'"
          answers:[ 'Crucifer','Calcifer','Calculator','Calcium' ]
          correctAnswer:1
     },
     {
          number:11
          question:"In The Wind Rises, why can't Jiro become a pilot?"
          answers:[ 'He is blind','He doesn\'t know how to drive one','He doesn\'t have enough money to go to college','He is nearsighted' ]
          correctAnswer:3
     },
     {
          number:12
          question:'Which character from Tales of Earthsea says, "Life without death is not life."'
          answers:[ 'Haitaka','Teru','Sparrowhawk','Hare' ]
          correctAnswer:0
     }

]
